=Just Fiancée= =Episode 20=
= مخطوبون للتو = = الحلقة 20 =
You mean...
أنت تعني...
Gu Manman...
قو مانمان ...
Killed herself?
قتلت نفسها؟
After she took
بعد أن أخذت
Max's blueprint for the Xiaolin Bay project,
مخطط ماكس لمشروع خليج شياولين ،
she gave it to her father
أعطته لأبيها
and went missing.
واختفى.
And I also heard
وسمعت أيضا
that her father is in Xiaolin Bay.
أن والدها في خليج Xiaolin.
What?
ماذا؟
If he thinks that Gu Manman's death
إذا كان يعتقد أن موت قو مانمان
has something to do with Su Yu,
له علاقة بـ Su Yu ،
then...
ومن بعد...
Su Yu would be in danger!
سوف تكون سو يو في خطر!
Let's call the police, Grandpa!
دعنا نتصل بالشرطة ، جدي!
But I don't have any concrete evidence.
لكن ليس لدي أي دليل ملموس.
No.
رقم.
I'm going there.
أنا ذاهب إلى هناك.
Don't!
لا!
Grandpa!
جدي!
You will only make things
سوف تصنع الأشياء فقط
more complicated if you go there.
أكثر تعقيدًا إذا ذهبت إلى هناك.
Luo Da is with him.
لوه دا معه.
So far he hasn't reported anything,
حتى الآن لم يبلغ عن أي شيء ،
which means they should be fine.
مما يعني أنهم يجب أن يكونوا بخير.
(No, I still think something will go wrong.)
(لا ، ما زلت أعتقد أن شيئًا ما سيحدث بشكل خاطئ.)
(Su Yu, I'm worried about you.)
(سو يو ، أنا قلق عليك.)
(If I told you about it,)
(إذا أخبرتك عن ذلك ،)
(you would have definitely told me not to come.)
(كنت ستخبرني بالتأكيد ألا أحضر).
(That is why I've decided to come on my own.)
(لهذا السبب قررت المجيء بمفردي).
Mr. Gu,
السيد.  قو
our men have picked up Miss Qiao.
لقد التقط رجالنا الآنسة تشياو.
Good, ask them to bring Qiao Mai over.
حسنًا ، اطلب منهم إحضار تشياو ماي.
You keep an eye on Su Yu.
أنت تراقب Su Yu.
Don't let him get away.
لا تدعه يبتعد.
Alright, Mr. Gu.
حسنًا ، سيد جو.
Where is Su Yu?
أين سو يو؟
Qiao Mai.
تشياو مي.
That's me.
هذا أنا.
Your step-parents
زوج أمك
are Wang Li
هم وانغ لي
and Qiao Ze.
وتشياو زي.
How did you find out about this?
كيف تعرف ذلك؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm your father,
أنا والدك،
as well as Gu Manman's father.
وكذلك والد قو مانمان.
You and Manman are twins.
أنت ومانمان توأمان.
We were poor back then
كنا فقراء في ذلك الوقت
and we couldn't afford to raise the both of you,
ولم نتمكن من رفع كلاكما ،
so your mother sent you away
لذلك أرسلتك والدتك بعيدا
and kept your elder sister with us.
واحتفظت بأختك الكبرى معنا.
This is my biggest regret in life.
هذا هو أكبر ندمي في الحياة.
My father
والدي
is Qiao Ze.
هو تشياو زي.
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
Where did you take Su Yu?
اين اخذت سو يو؟
Tell me now!
أخبرني الآن!
Mr. Su Yu, the chairman of Max Group,
السيد سو يو ، رئيس مجموعة ماكس ،
went to Xiaolin Bay on the pretense
ذهب إلى خليج Xiaolin بدعوى
of investing and surveying,
للاستثمار والمسح ،
and violently beat up the local villagers,
واعتدوا بالضرب المبرح على القرويين المحليين ،
forcing them to sell their land to Max Group.
إجبارهم على بيع أراضيهم لمجموعة ماكس.
The investigation of the matter is ongoing.
التحقيق في هذه المسألة مستمر.
Luo Da,
لو دا ،
what is this all about?
حول ماذا يدور كل هذا؟
Chairman,
رئيس،
your reputation in the company
سمعتك في الشركة
has been tarnished.
تم تلطيخها.
Because you attacked the villagers,
لأنك هاجمت القرويين ،
the company's stock prices
أسعار أسهم الشركة
have hit rock bottom.
وصلت إلى الحضيض.
I see.
أرى.
We shouldn't stay in Xiaolin Bay any longer.
لا ينبغي أن نبقى في خليج شياولين بعد الآن.
Let's go back.
دعنا نعود.
Hold it!
أمسك به!
Chairman,
رئيس،
you won't be able to leave now.
لن تتمكن من المغادرة الآن.
Mr. Gu
السيد.  قو
wants to see you.
يريد رؤيتك.
Her disappearance
اختفائها
has something to do
لديه ما يفعله
with her father, Gu Tianlin.
مع والدها ، قو تيانلين.